MATT GARVIN

UX Consulting

Interaction Designer

Information Architect

PROFILE

User-centered researcher and designer with a demonstrated history in a variety of industries including hospitality and supply chain logistics. Skilled in contextual inquiry, UX consulting, design strategy, interaction design, rapid prototyping, information architecture, usability needs and evaluation.

CONTACT

- **248.797.4279**
- mtthwgrvn@gmail.com
- mtthwx.com

EXPERIENCE

UX Consultant | mtthwx.com

2018 - CURRENT

Freelance UX research and design consulting.

Account Manager | N&C

8/2017 - 4/2019

Freight auditing and account management, audit project manager and trainer.

Bartender | Cliff Bell's

8/2012 - 5/2016

High volume jazz club, fine-dining and craft cocktails

SKILLS

- User Research
- Information Architecture
- Rapid Prototyping
- Wireframes
- Visual Communication
- Empathy
- Ethnography

Bartender | BD's Mongolian Grill

2006 - 2011 (2016)

After opening the Oldsmar, FL location in 2006, I moved back to Michigan and transferred to Royal Oak. From there I went on to become a lead server (mentor), head bartender and supervisor. I left in 2011 to help open an upscale casual lounge called Gemmayze in Royal Oak, but periodically returned to BD's to pick up shifts and fill in gaps particularly around the holidays through 2016. Many of the teammates I've trained went on to become bar and restaurant managers in other establishments.

EDUCATION

BA Anthropology | WSU

2011-2017

Honors college transfer, peer mentor, president of undergrad anthro learning community.

MS Information | UMSI

2019-2021

Specializing in UX/HCI/Social Computing research and design consulting